tanishq.co.in 2019-07-10

# PrivacyPolicy

## Privacy Policy

Titan Company Limited (“Titan”, “We”, “Us”) is committed to the compliance of applicable Privacy Laws in the country where Titan’s product is distributed. Protecting the privacy and security of your personal data is of prime importance to Titan, therefore, we conduct our business by abiding by the laws applicable on data privacy and data security in the country where Titan’s product is distributed to you.

This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you about the personal data that is collected from you, how your personal data may be used and disclosed, how you can control the use of your personal data, and how your personal data is protected when you use the Titan Application or the application developed by a third party for Titan (“Application”). We do not sell trade your personally identifiable information; however, we may share the same with third parties who assist us in conducting our business, operating our website/Application, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

What Information is collected about you:

_Information you provide directly:_

When you use certain functions provided by the Application, such as when you register for certain services, access, features or services, we may ask you to provide certain personal data such as name, contact number, postal address, email address, username, password etc.

_Information that is automatically collected when you visit the Application:_

a. When you download and visit the application, certain information may be collected automatically, which includes:

b. Your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) Address,

c. Your browser type and operating system,

d. Web pages and links you visit, advertisements you view,

e. Your bandwidth speed and information about the about the software programs that are installed on your computer,

f. Standard server log information

_Information that we collect from other sources:_

We may receive information about you from publicly and commercially available sources (as permitted by law), which we may combine with other information we receive from or about you. We also may receive information about you from third-party social networking services when you choose to connect with those services.

How we use the information we collect:

  * _General:  Titan may use the information collected from you to register you or your device for a Service, to provide a service or feature you request, to provide customized content and make recommendations based on your past activities on our Application._
  * _Advertisements:  Titan may use your information to provide you with product and service updates, newsletters and other communications about existing and/or new products and services by post, email, telephone, in-device messaging and/or text message (SMS), if you have provided your prior consent or we are otherwise permitted to do so under applicable law._
  * _Statistics and Research:  Titan may use your information to create user group profiles or segment data and to otherwise create anonymous, aggregated statistics about the use of our products, services and loyalty programs, which we may share with third parties and/or make available to the public._
  * _Product/Services Improvement:  Titan may use your information to improve and enhance existing Titan products, services and Applications and develop new offerings, recommendations, advertisements and other communications and learn more about customers’ preferences in general._
  * _Publish your reviews, comments and content: Where you have uploaded product reviews, comments or content to our websites or Application and made them publicly visible, Titan may link to, publish or publicize these materials elsewhere including in our own advertisements._

Titan may use the information collected from you to register you or your device for a Service, to provide a service or feature you request, to provide customized content and make recommendations based on your past activities on our Application.

Titan may use your information to provide you with product and service updates, newsletters and other communications about existing and/or new products and services by post, email, telephone, in-device messaging and/or text message (SMS), if you have provided your prior consent or we are otherwise permitted to do so under applicable law.

Titan may use your information to create user group profiles or segment data and to otherwise create anonymous, aggregated statistics about the use of our products, services and loyalty programs, which we may share with third parties and/or make available to the public.

Titan may use your information to improve and enhance existing Titan products, services and Applications and develop new offerings, recommendations, advertisements, and other communications and learn more about customers’ preferences in general.

Where you have uploaded product reviews, comments or content to our websites or Application and made them publicly visible, Titan may link to, publish or publicize these materials elsewhere including in our own advertisements.

To whom do we disclose your Personal Data:

a. We may employ third party entities and individuals to facilitate our Services (e.g. maintenance, analysis, audit, marketing, and development). These third parties have limited access to your information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated to Titan, not to disclose or use it for other purposes. All of our approved third-party providers go through an extensive data protection compliance vetting process before being selected as a third party provider and are bound by all relevant data privacy laws, terms of confidentiality, and this Privacy Policy.

b. If you choose to use the Application, you will be asked to confirm acceptance of the third party developer user agreement and Titan’s privacy policy.

c. There may be instances when we disclose your information to other parties to comply with the law or respond to compulsory legal process or to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Services or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Titan, or any of our respective affiliates, business partners, or customers.

Your Choices:

We offer a variety of choices about how we use your information. You can make choices about whether to receive promotional communications from us by following the unsubscribe instructions included in the communication. In addition, you can also generally make choices in your settings, or by visiting relevant links.

Security:

The security of your personal data is of great importance to us. We have put in place reasonable physical and technical measures to safeguard the information we collect in connection with the Services. However, please note that although we take reasonable steps to protect your information, no Application/website, Internet transmission, computer system or wireless connection is completely secure.

Links to Other Web Sites:

Titan Application may contain links to other websites. Titan is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites or applications.

On our Application, we may have links to other websites/ applications or you are referred to our Application through a link from another website or Application. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites or applications. Such content is subject to their terms of use and any additional guidelines and privacy information provided in relation to that use on their website or application. We recommend that you check the policy of each website/application you visit to better understand your rights and obligations especially when you are submitting any type of content on those third party website/application. Please contact the owner or operator of such website/application if you have any concerns or questions.

Changes to the Privacy Policy:

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time to reflect changes in our practices and service offerings. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will update the date on which the new Privacy Policy will be effective. We will notify you of any material changes in the way we treat your information by placing a prominent notice on our website/Application.
